const questions = [
    {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "Which team is Iceman a part of?",
        "options": [
            "The X-Men",
            "The Fantastic Four",
            "The Invaders",
            "The Liberators"
        ],
        "answer": "The X-Men",
        "heroId": 1009362
    },
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "In the X-Men, what substance is Wolverine's skeleton made of?",
        "options": [
            "Cavorite",
            "Vibranium",
            "Adamantium",
            "Neutronium"
        ],
        "answer": "Adamantium",
        "heroId": 1009718
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "What is the name of Spider-Man, who first appeared in 1962?",
        "options": [
            "Tom Parker",
            "John Parker",
            "Peter Parker",
            "Alan Parker"
        ],
        "answer": "Peter Parker",
        "heroId": 1009610
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "What was Wolverine called when he was a Horseman of Apocalypse?",
        "options": [
            "Rage",
            "Death",
            "Destruction",
            "Oblivion"
        ],
        "answer": "Death",
        "heroId": 1009718
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "Which superhero is never without his hammer forged by dwarfs?",
        "options": [
            "Bizarro",
            "Flash",
            "Venom",
            "Thor"
        ],
        "answer": "Thor",
        "heroId": 1009664
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "What color is associated with Hulk?",
        "options": [
            "Yellow",
            "Red",
            "Green",
            "Blue"
        ],
        "answer": "Green",
        "heroId": 1009351
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "Which superhero looks like a being made of stone?",
        "options": [
            "Plastic Man",
            "The Thing",
            "Hawkman",
            "Superboy"
        ],
        "answer": "The Thing",
        "heroId": 1009662
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "Whose butler is Edwin Jarvis?",
        "options": [
            "Bruce Wayne",
            "Charles Xavier",
            "Tony Stark",
            "Henry Steven"
        ],
        "answer": "Tony Stark",
        "heroId": 1009368
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "Which superhero wears a costume inspired by the American flag?",
        "options": [
            "Tigra",
            "Blade",
            "Iron Man",
            "Captain America"
        ],
        "answer": "Captain America",
        "heroId": 1009220
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "Including his thumbs, how many fingers on both hands does The Thing have?",
        "options": [
            8,
            6,
            10,
            4
        ],
        "answer": 8,
        "heroId": 1009662
    }
]

module.exports={
    questions
}